

RPA Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Robotic Process Automation, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution Architecture, Automation Anywhere, SQL Server, VB Script



Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: RPA Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Robotic Process Automation, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution

Architecture, Automation Anywhere, SQL Server, VB Script

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Overall, 4 years of Experience in IT Industry and 2.5 years of relevant Automation Anywhere.

Certification in Advanced RPA Automation Anywhere V11.0.

Created end to end automation solutions for clients as per requirement which involves development, testing and deployment of automation by using Automation Anywhere.

Having extensive knowledge on Automation Anywhere.

Experience in all phases of Software Development Life Cycle with Analysis, Development, Testing, and Deploying. Multi-cultured Team Player with complete flexibility to work independently as well as in a team and have quick grasping capabilities to work with the newly emerging technologies.

Having basic knowledge on Python and VBScript programming.

Have exposure in A2019

Work Experience

CTD Techs as RPA Developer

Feb 2020 to Jul 2020

Did End-End Bot development using V11

CTD Techs as RPA Developer

Feb 2020 to Jul 2020

End to End Process & Documentation Preparation

CTD Techs as RPA Developer

Feb 2020 to Jul 2020

Optis Information Services India Pvt Ltd, as RPA Developer

Sep 2017 to Feb 2020

HP Pvt Ltd, as Software Engineer

Jun 2013 to Aug 2014

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Pdit college of engineering in 2010

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	ast Used Experience	
Automation Anywhere	11	2020	2 Year(s) 1 Month(s)	
Automation Anywhere	A2019	2020	5 Month(s)	
WINDOWS	XP,8,10	2021	10 Year(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			
Kannada	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time